netsertive.com 2016-04-09

# Privacy - Netsertive

Last Updated: 8.27.13

Netsertive, Inc. (“Netsertive”, the “Company,” “us,” “we,” or “our”) is committed to protecting the privacy of users (“user”, “you” or “your”) of our website (“Site”), [netsertive.com](http://netsertive.com/), and our products and services (“Product” or “Products”). Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our Site and our Products.  This Privacy Policy will be continuously assessed against new technologies, business practices and our clients’ needs.  This Privacy Policy applies to this Site and our Products and governs data collection and usage at this Site and our Products.

User Consent

By visiting [netsertive.com](http://netsertive.com/) or using our Products, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.  You expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information (as defined below) according to this Privacy Policy.  Personal Information may be processed by Netsertive or Netsertive’s trusted vendors or other third parties in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent.

Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

Netsertive is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.  We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily.  The Personal Information we collect includes, but is not limited to, the following: name, mailing address, Web address, telephone number, e-mail address, and information contained in any e-mail or other communication you send to us or information you give to us in any other way, as well as, information required for the payment for products or services that you order from us, including credit card numbers, security codes and other financial information (collectively, “Personal Information”).  We do not sell or rent Personal Information to anyone.  Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we strive to keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties.

As you use our Site or Products, certain passive information may also be collected, including your Internet Protocol address, browser type, and operating system.  We also use cookies, web beacons and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed.  This type of information is collected to make our Products more useful to you.

Third party vendors, including Google, Yahoo, and Microsoft, show you ads on sites on the internet.  These vendors use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to the Site.  Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the Google [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) or other third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). 

How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any Personal Information, to deliver products or services, or purchase website marketing services, to present our Website and its contents to you, to facilitate your request for a quote from a third party service provider or to aid us in serving you better.  If you purchase products or services from Netsertive, we may transmit your Personal Information to payment processors.  We may use your Personal Information to contact you directly by electronic newsletter, promotional e-mail, and telephone with additional information and offers about our products and services and to carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.  We may also use the information that you provide in any other way that we describe when you provide the information and for any other purpose with your consent.

Disclosure of Your Information

We may convert or combine some Personal Information of users into de-identified or aggregated data that does not disclose any of the Personal Information of any individual user.  We may disclose any such de-identified or aggregated data without restriction. 

We may disclose Personal Information to our subsidiaries and affiliates and to any contractors, service providers and other third parties who need to know such information to support our permitted uses of Personal Information.  We may disclose such Personal  Information to a buyer or other successor to our business in the event of a sale of equity or assets, reorganization, merger or a similar corporate transaction.

Some of the information that we collect from cookies relates to your personal use of the Site and our Products allows us to store information about your preferences, speed up your searches and recognize you when you return to our Site or Products.  Except as otherwise expressly provided in this policy, this information is not shared with third parties.  Other information that we collect from cookies and web beacons is not tied to your Personal Information and enables us to estimate our audience size and usage patterns.  This traffic data may be shared with third parties. 

We may also disclose your Personal Information for any other purpose disclosed when the information is provided, and for any other purpose with your consent.

We may also disclose your Personal Information to comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request and to enforce or apply our terms of use or terms of sale, including for billing and collection purposes, or if we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of our customers or others.  This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may contact us at any time at [privacy@netsertive.com](mailto:privacy@netsertive.com) to:

  1.  See what Personal Information we have about you, if any.
  2. Change/correct any Personal Information we have about you.
  3.  Request that we delete any Personal Information we have about you, except if doing so conflicts with ongoing business between you and Netsertive.
  4.  Express any concern you have about our use of your Personal Information.
  5. Ask questions about our privacy policy and changes we have made. 

Advertising

Netsertive may display re-targeted ads to our Site across the Internet to you.  We collect non‐personally identifiable information about your visits to our Website, and your interaction with our Products.  No personally identifiable information is collected in this process.  If you do not want Netsertive to collect this information, you may opt out of re-targeting.  Opting out will not in any way affect your use of our Site and our Products.  To opt‐out of re-targeting, please visit the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). 

Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your Personal Information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure.  All information that you provide to us is stored on servers behind firewalls and certain Personal Information will be encrypted using secure socket layer (SSL) technology. 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you.  When we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Site and Products, you are responsible for choosing a secure password and keeping this password confidential.  We ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure.  Although we have implemented security measures that we think are adequate, we cannot guarantee the security of your Personal Information transmitted to our site.  Any transmission of Personal Information is at your own risk.  We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. 

Notification of Changes

We post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page.  If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ Personal Information, we may notify you by e-mail to the primary e-mail address specified in your account and/or through a notice on our Site and Products.  The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page.  You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our site and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

Children Under the Age of Thirteen 

Our Site and Products are not intended for children under 13 years of age, and no one under age 13 may provide any information to this Site.  We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13.  If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Site, make any purchases through this Site, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Site or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use.  If we learn we have collected or received Personal Information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information.  If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [privacy@netsertive.com](mailto:privacy@netsertive.com).   

Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Site that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of Personal Information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [privacy@netsertive.com](mailto:privacy@netsertive.com). 

Users Outside of the United States

Our Site is hosted in the United States and our Products are delivered from the United States.  It is possible that certain information will be stored on servers in multiple other countries on the “cloud” or other similar distributed hosting platforms.  If you are a user accessing our Site or Products from the European Union, Asia or any other region with laws governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please note that you are transferring your Personal Information outside your home jurisdiction, and that by providing your Personal Information you are consenting to the transfer of your Personal Information to the United States and other jurisdictions as indicated above, and to our use of your Personal Information in accordance with this policy.

Acceptance of Privacy Policy

By using the Site and our Products , you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site or Products.  Your continued use of this Site and our Products following posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, you may send an email to [privacy@netsertive.com](mailto:privacy@netsertive.com).
